Guide to the George McTurnan Kahin papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
Kahin, George McTurnan papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
- Series XIII. Vietnam
  - Elections (Box 73, Folder 42)
    - Elections, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 47)
  - Indochina War Information (Box 73, Folder 48)
    - Reagan & Schultz on Vietnam (Box 73, Folder 49)
    - Westmoreland--NLF figures (Box 73, Folder 50)
    - Newspaper clips (Box 73, Folder 51)
  - Saigon-Notes Jan 1970 (Box 73, Folder 52)
    - GK notes, Jan 1970 (Box 73, Folder 53)
    - Cornell, May, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 54)
  - Vietnam-Notes, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 55)
  - Vietnam: Memo (Box 73, Folder 56)
    - Memo for Fulbright & Kraft, Aug 1971 (Box 73, Folder 57)
    - Ha Van Lau, Pham Van Dong and NLF official (Box 73, Folder 58)
  - Presidents to North Vietnam (Box 73, Folder 59)
    - Bolling & Whitmore, Aug 1971 (Box 73, Folder 60)
  - North Vietnam:1972, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 61)
    - North Vietnam: Sept 1972 (Box 73, Folder 62)
    - Duplicates of Notes: Thailand, S. Vietnam, June 1972 (Box 73, Folder 63)
    - Hanoi, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 64)
    - Paris 1972 (Box 73, Folder 65)
    - Paris-Oct 27, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 66)
  - Material for Jan 1994 V.N. Trip (Box 73, Folder 67)
  - Recounts from individuals (Box 73, Folder 68)
    - Pfeiffer (Box 73, Folder 69)
    - David Schoenbrun (Box 73, Folder 70)
  - 1960's (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - 1972 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - 1980's (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - 1990's (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Thomas (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Series XIV. Burma
  - Burma 1950s-1960s (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Burma 1950s (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Burma 1953 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Burma 1945-1953 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Burma 1947-1952 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Burma n.d. (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Burma 1955-1956 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Burma Feb. 18, 1980-March 2, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Burma-Course Material-Spring 1955 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - summer school (Box 74, Folder 20)
- Series XV. Malaysia & Singapore & Indonesia
  - Sabah (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Singapore (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Government 314, April 29, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - U. of Singapore & Nanyang U. (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Nanyang 1976 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Nanyang 1977 (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Nanyang 1978 (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - U. of Singapore 1976 (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - U. of Singapore 1977 (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - U. of Singapore 1978 (Box 74, Folder 30)
    - U. of Singapore 1979 (Box 74, Folder 31)
    - Receipts (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - External Financing of the V.N. War (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Receipts (Box 74, Folder 34)
    - Extra Receipts 1981-1982 trip (Box 74, Folder 35)
    - Trip:GK (Box 74, Folder 36)
  - Bibliographies (Box 74, Folder 37)
    - Cambodia & Laos:1970 (Box 74, Folder 38)
    - Research Materials:Vietnam (Box 74, Folder 39)
  - Govt 304-Indonesia (Box 74, Folder 40)
  - Indonesia Revision Materials (Box 74, Folder 41)
  - Village Research (Box 74, Folder 42)
    - Paponan (Box 74, Folder 43)
    - Ranujoso-5 Schedules (Box 74, Folder 44)
    - Kedjosan-7 schedules (Box 74, Folder 45)
    - Djogomertan-5 (Box 74, Folder 46)
  - FES 601-Indonesia, 1961 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Indonesia Seminar-National Unity (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Islam (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Indonesia Revision Draft (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - FES 601-Indonesia (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Indonesia I, Nov 30,1959 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Indonesia II, May 3, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Indonesia III (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Spread of Islam into Indonesia (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Islam I (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - FES 601 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Indonesia I-Historical Background (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Indonesia II (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Indonesia II-Historical Development to 1945 (Box 75, Folder 14)
- Series XVI. Presidential Libraries
  - FOI Act Amendment, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Carrolton Press:Microfiche on Vietnam (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Microfiche:G.M.T.K. (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Declassified Documents Reference, July1979-Sept.1980 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - National Security Archive-Scott Armstrong (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - National Security Archive-Request to (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - National Archives, Wash. D.C. (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Archives: Wash. D.C. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Kahin Olin Ms Collection (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - G.M.T.K-Appeal, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - M.R. requests, July 1977 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Examples of Difficulties in securing declassification (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - State Dep't Files (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Forcier (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Hoover Library (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - H.P. Jones (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Lansdale Collection (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Council on Foreign Relations Archive (N.Y.C.) (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Freedom of Information Act (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Public Record Office:Kew (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Public Record Office:England, May 1983 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Truman Library (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Truman:Duplicates of Interesting Docs. (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Hurley-O.S.S. Vietnam, 1945 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - NSC #68, May 1983 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Truman Russia(& US Foreign Policy) (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Truman: Burma (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Truman: Cambodia (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Truman: China (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Truman: Thailand (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Eisenhower (Box 71, Folder 32)
    - Dulles Papers, Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 33)
    - Oral Histories (Box 71, Folder 34)
  - Eisenhower Library & Columbia (Declassified) (Box 71, Folder 35)
    - Document Request Forms, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 36)
    - Eisenhower Library Visit, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 37)
    - Mandatory Review Requests, June 1981 (Box 71, Folder 38)
    - Notes on Eisenhower Diaries (Box 71, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence Eisenhower (Box 71, Folder 40)
  - Eisenhower:Laos (Box 71, Folder 41)
    - US-Laos Policy (Box 71, Folder 42)
    - Laos:Sit. Reps, Jan 1961 (Box 71, Folder 43)
  - Dulles Collection-Princeton (Box 71, Folder 44)
    - Princeton (Box 71, Folder 45)
  - Columbia Oral Histories (Box 71, Folder 46)
  - Eisenhower Policy (Box 71, Folder 47)
    - Policy-Vietnam, April 2, 1954 (Box 71, Folder 48)
    - US-China Policy vis 2 vis Sea, May 1954 (Box 71, Folder 49)
    - Policy-Global, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 50)
  - Eisenhower:Burma (Box 71, Folder 51)
    - Eisenhower:Burma Neutralism (Box 71, Folder 52)
    - Eisenhower:Burma US-Burma Policy (Box 71, Folder 53)
  - Eisenhower:Cambodia (Box 71, Folder 54)
    - Eisenhower:Cambodia Khmer Serei (Box 71, Folder 55)
    - Eisenhower:Cambodia US-Cambodia Policy (Box 71, Folder 56)
  - Eisenhower:Indonesia (Box 71, Folder 57)
  - Eisenhower:Thailand (Box 71, Folder 58)
  - Kennedy Library (Box 71, Folder 59)
    - JFK:Mandatory Review Thailand &Vietnam (Box 71, Folder 60)
    - Mandatory Review Requested & underway (Box 71, Folder 61)
    - JFK (Box 71, Folder 62)
    - Zero Orders JFK (Box 71, Folder 63)
    - JFK Turn Downs-Not Appealed (Box 71, Folder 64)
    - Kennedy:New (Box 71, Folder 65)
  - Kennedy Current, 1978-1979 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Martin McGann, July23, 1981 March10, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Burke, John R (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Martin McGann, Sept25, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Kennedy Library, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Requests for Declassified Docs to be made in Sept-Oct 1980 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Letter to Megan (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Mass Correspodence, July-Sept 1978 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - New M.R. Procedures, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Oral History (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Hilsman Collection, 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - JFK:NSC Meetings Index (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - President's Officer Files (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Kennedy:National Security Files (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Weekend Readings (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - What was accomplished and what remains to be done (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - JFK (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Visit of June23-24,1977 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - June 23-24, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Kennedy-M.R. Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - MR Document Inventories (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Appeal of May 26, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Thomson Collection:Inventory (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Thomson Papers (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Briefings Washington DC, Green Thrush, May 18-20, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Anderson, Bruns Mozing (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Cambodia-Senate, May 14-15, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Cambo-Chron, Origs (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - JFF-Cambodia, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Kennedy:Indonesia (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - Indonesia Reports, Oct 1962/Jan 1980 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - JFK-Indonesia, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 33)
    - Balance of Payments Analysis & US Aid Program, 1962-3 (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - Kennedy:Cuba (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - Kennedy-Thailand new(post1980) data (Box 72, Folder 36)
    - Laos, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 37)
  - Laos-Chron 1961 (Box 72, Folder 38)
    - Laos-Jan 61', Jan, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 39)
    - Laos-Feb 61', Feb, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 40)
    - Laos-Mar 61', Mar, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 41)
    - Laos-April 61', April, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 42)
    - Laos-May 61', May, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 43)
    - Laos-June 61', June, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 44)
    - Laos-July 61', July, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 45)
    - Laos-Aug 61', Aug, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 46)
    - Laos-Sept 61', Sept, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 47)
    - Laos-Oct 61', Oct, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 48)
    - Laos-Nov 61', Nov, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 49)
  - Laos-Chron 1962 (Box 72, Folder 50)
    - Laos-Jan-June 62', Jan-June, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 51)
    - Laos-July-Dec 62' (Box 72, Folder 52)
  - Settlement (Box 72, Folder 53)
  - New:Unbound 1980:Laos (Box 72, Folder 54)
    - Laos:Subsequent to Binding, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 55)
    - Laos:Subsequent to Binding 1963 (Box 72, Folder 56)
  - Lyndon Baines Johnson Library (Box 72, Folder 57)
    - LBJ:Current 1980 (Box 72, Folder 58)
    - Martin Elzy:1980-1 (Box 72, Folder 59)
    - LBJ:David Humphrey 1981-88, 1981-1988 (Box 72, Folder 60)
    - Grant-in-Aid Application (Box 72, Folder 61)
    - Trip:April 27-May 2, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 62)
    - A Future Visit:1979 or 1980? (Box 72, Folder 63)
    - Johnson Library (Box 72, Folder 64)
    - LBJ:Current Appeal (Box 72, Folder 65)
    - LBJ:Current Requests (Box 72, Folder 66)
    - New LBJ Inventories Unused (Box 72, Folder 67)
    - LBJ (Box 72, Folder 68)
  - LBJ: Visits, 1975 & 1976 (Box 72, Folder 69)
    - LBJ Aug 1975 Visit (Box 72, Folder 70)
    - LBJ August, 1976 Visit (Box 72, Folder 71)
    - LBJ-old correspondence (Box 72, Folder 72)
    - LBJ-Nov 1978 (Box 72, Folder 73)
    - White house Central Files (Inventory:Nov 1979 V.N. & Indonesia) (Box 72, Folder 74)
  - Oral Histories-LBJ Library (Box 72, Folder 75)
  - LBJ Burma (Box 72, Folder 76)
  - Cambodia 1964-1965 (Box 72, Folder 77)
    - Cambodia:Available Oct17, 1980, but not yet ordered (Box 72, Folder 78)
  - Laos 1964-1965 (Box 72, Folder 79)
  - Pauer:Rand Study-May, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 80)
  - LBJ Indonesia (Box 72, Folder 81)
    - Church Com. Records (Box 72, Folder 82)
  - LBJ Philippines (Box 72, Folder 83)